<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://vasu.fyi/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 14:51:17 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vasu.fyi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://vasu.fyi/page/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 14:51:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vasu.fyi/page/links/</guid>
      <description>Awesomeness  Awesome - Link to Awesomenes. Awesome Modern C&amp;#43;&amp;#43; - Curated list of awesome modern C++ resources  Blogs  Fluent C&amp;#43;&amp;#43; - An excellent resource for writing expressive code in C++ High Scalability Morning Dew  Newsletters  The Browser - Daily curated newsletter  Tools  VS Code - My go to text editor CLion - Trying out this C++ editor Balsamiq - Great tool for wireframes  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>https://vasu.fyi/page/slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 08:42:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vasu.fyi/page/slides/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my slides.
As I learn, I find it easy to take notes in a markdown file. I&#39;ve turned my notes into slides using Reveal.js. This is an excellent presentation framework built in HTML / Javascript. You can build excellent presentations off your markdown files.
I plan to convert more of my notes into slide in the days to come. Stay tuned &amp;hellip;
Design / Architecture  SOLID - Object oriented design principles (Robert C Martin)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://vasu.fyi/page/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 15:37:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vasu.fyi/page/resume/</guid>
      <description>This browser does not support PDFs. Please download the PDF to view it: Download PDF.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://vasu.fyi/page/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 11:01:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vasu.fyi/page/books/</guid>
      <description>Currently Reading       In Queue       Bookshelf                                           </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prelude</title>
      <link>https://vasu.fyi/posts/prelude/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 22:20:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vasu.fyi/posts/prelude/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m passionate about technology in general and programming. My first introduction to computers was in my junior year of High School when my parents got us Sinclair ZX Spectrum 128K.
While I primarily used it for playing games, I did get to code simple BASIC programs. Never did I imagine then it would end up as a Software Engineer. I went on to finish my Masters (Computer Applications) and over the years I&#39;ve worked with multitude of technologies, languages, frameworks and tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello</title>
      <link>https://vasu.fyi/posts/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 22:18:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vasu.fyi/posts/hello/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m Vasu Balakrishnan, a passionate technologist, software development leader and technical architect.
Welcome to my site. Stay tuned for updates, as I curate the content &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vasu.fyi/slides/design/solid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vasu.fyi/slides/design/solid/</guid>
      <description>SOLID Solid Principles of Object Oriented Programming to make software designs more understandable, flexible and maintenable
 SRP Single Responsibility Principle
 A class should&#39;ve a single responsibility
   OCP Open Closed Principle
 Types should be open for extension, but closed for modification
   LSP Liskov Subsitution Principle
 Objects in a program should be replaceable with instances of their sub-type without altering correctness of that program</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://vasu.fyi/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vasu.fyi/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Accomplished software development leader and a passionate technologist dedicated to continuous learning and professional growth.
When I&#39;m not working, I love to bike, hike, play badminton or ping-pong.
Disclaimer: The opinions expressed herein are my own personal opinions and do not represent my employer’s view in any way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>