<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on </title>
    <link>https://vasu.fyi/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 14:51:17 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vasu.fyi/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://vasu.fyi/page/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 14:51:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vasu.fyi/page/links/</guid>
      <description>Awesomeness  Awesome - Link to Awesomenes. Awesome Modern C&amp;#43;&amp;#43; - Curated list of awesome modern C++ resources Awesome Distributed Systems  Blogs  Fluent C&amp;#43;&amp;#43; - An excellent resource for writing expressive code in C++ High Scalability Morning Dew  Interview Prep  System Design Tech Interview Handbook leetcode Kevin Naughton Jr&amp;#39;s github Interview Cake Educative IO Hired in Tech  Newsletters  The Browser - Daily curated newsletter  Tools  VS Code - My go to text editor CLion - Trying out this C++ editor Balsamiq - Great tool for wireframes  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>https://vasu.fyi/page/slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 08:42:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vasu.fyi/page/slides/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my slides.
As I learn, I find it easy to take notes in a markdown file. I&#39;ve turned my notes into slides using Reveal.js. This is an excellent presentation framework built in HTML / Javascript. You can build excellent presentations off your markdown files.
I plan to convert more of my notes into slide in the days to come. Stay tuned &amp;hellip;
Design / Architecture  SOLID - Object oriented design principles (Robert C Martin)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://vasu.fyi/page/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 15:37:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vasu.fyi/page/resume/</guid>
      <description>This browser does not support PDFs. Please download the PDF to view it: Download PDF.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://vasu.fyi/page/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 11:01:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vasu.fyi/page/books/</guid>
      <description>Currently Reading         In Queue       Bookshelf                                           </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://vasu.fyi/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vasu.fyi/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Accomplished software development leader and a passionate technologist dedicated to continuous learning and professional growth.
When I&#39;m not working, I love to bike, hike, play badminton or ping-pong.
Disclaimer: The opinions expressed herein are my own personal opinions and do not represent my employer’s view in any way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>